# Rayan Nawzat Rashad

**UX/UI** Designer

## **Summary**

Energetic UI/UX Designer with over 1 year of experience designing websites and apps through emphasizing to get an idea about what people care about, defining the problem and work on solutions through sketching, wireframing, and visual designing before testing it with potential users to see how they react to it.

## Experience

## RevPanda - UI/UX Designer | Full-time

2022/9-Current

an awards winning result-driven digital marketing agency with years of experience in Brand Management, Design, SEO Services, Link Building and more.

- Working on multiple projects in different fields.
- Collaborating with product managers, SEO team, content team, heads of departments, and developers to help achieve our goals and needs.

# **ExTrac** - UX Designer | Full-time

2022/5-2022/7

ExTrac is a humanitarian Conflict Tracker product that organizes, triangulates, and visualizes longitudinal data on conflict activity and risk. Synergizing live feeds of text and imagery pulled directly from hard-to-reach online networks, it offers granular insight into adversary attack techniques, material capabilities, and targeting priorities.

- Managed the UX design of the new service system.
- Responsible for User research, Personas, Wireframe.

# Dal Agency- UX/UI Designer | Project based

2021/12 - 2022/5

Dal Agency is a full-service and a leading destination company providing digital solutions for all types of visual design systems including branding, digital marketing, UI/UX design, and social media management.

- Worked on 2 different projects for the agency as the UX/UI designer.
- Took responsibility for the whole UI/UX process while implementing the brand and identity design into the UI.

## Freelancer - UX/UI Designer

2021/7 -2021/12

- Worked individually on designing an Influencer's website for (<u>The.murt</u>) The project stopped for a while and currently working on developing it.
- individually designed movies & shows info mobile application called (<u>Movieshow</u>) The project went through +12 different steps in 4 weeks before reaching the final version.

### Personal info

Rayan.n.rashad@gmail.com

- +964 7713634903 (What's App)
- +90 5318707826

Dribble Behance LinkedIn

#### Education

#### Re:Coded & Flatiron School

Online / Remote 01/2021 - 05/2021

- + UX/UI Design Bootcamp
- + Intensive 4-Months bootcamp with real-world capstone project
- + Creates powerful lifelong network

# Koya University - Faculty of Education

Bachelor's in English Education Erbil, Iraq 2017 - 2021

#### Skills

Tools	Technical skills
Figma Adobe XD Illustrator Photoshop InVision Mural Notion ClickUp	Interaction design Visual design Wireframing Prototyping Researching Problem solving Personas Design thinking
Languages	Interpersonal skills

Arabic, Leadership
Native Public speaking
Contextual Inquiry
English, Task managing
Professional

Kurdish, Very Good